Hello, hello friends, such people have
contracted to give a share chilli of dividend,
so even if you have not yet come and changed,
you can still have MS Word,
which date did you have to take from to go inside this video,
then you can turn off NFC
for the department, so friends,
before starting the video, subscribe to our channel, if you liked the
video then
definitely like it and friends, press the bell icon so that if we
bring any video related to it, you will get its notification
quickly and there will be no side effects,
dominant also, think like this, it has returned, it is
running above 1469, now friends,
for one month, it bends at absolutely soft
1469 time, so it was IS,
15204 minutes meeting is a little less than it is,
hence there is a problem of folk drama, so who
can make this, so friends,
its record is one, it has been kept on 1956
and there is only one record, and 18th March means
before 18th March, the
share should be returned from ICL in our demat account  Only then
we will get
provident fund, so before getting angry
we have three days, 15 16 and 17, we
can change anytime between 15 16 17 and
till 17th we should have more shares in our demat account, only then
we will
get dividend of thousand rupees, so those who do not have shares with friends can
also be more successful, if we
buy our shares between 15 16 17 and
jointly invest 15000
then we will get dividend of ₹40
and friends to give dividend of ₹100
I will mix with Lakhpati at ₹3000, so to
get dividend of ₹10 would you like to pay 30 to 25
thousand or not, now this is our
advantage in this, if the share rises till here then
you will get profit from that too, right
and the separation of Gopi share is right,
people of this month chew on this and
get 120 prices 1469  Rupees is today's method,
so let me tell you in oil, last and
theatre, if you want to take this jail then till 17th March,
you have three last salaries, 15, 16, 17,
you have one, it
is activated on the 18th and there
is a request on the 19th, so our 18th and before that we are
ready that this city should be inside,
friends, how did you like our video, if you liked the video then
definitely like it and subscribe to the channel
and press the bell icon so that
this latest video reaches you, I am smart, see you
next 9